https://campmohawk.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Children’s Privacy
The Children’s Online Privacy Act (COPPA) protects the personal information of children under the age of 13. This applies to individually identifiable information about a child that is collected online, such as full name, home address, e-mail address, telephone number or any other information that would allow someone to identify or contact the child. The Act and Rule also cover other types of information collected through cookies or other types of tracking mechanisms when they are tied to individually identifiable information. It is important for you to understand this law. We encourage you to read more about COPPA.
Privacy Policy
YMCA Camp Mohawk, Inc. is committed to providing a safe and secure online experience for families who visit our site. We are dedicated to safeguarding any personal information collected on line and to helping parents and children have positive experiences on the internet. Consistent with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without parental consent. YMCA Camp Mohawk, Inc. only collects information necessary to send participants and prospective campers marketing information about the camp and to inform camper’s families of events at Mohawk.
“Cookies”
YMCA Camp Mohawk, Inc. does not collect personal information about users or how they use the site. Mohawk also does not use the information tracking made possible through “cookies”, small pieces of data that may be sent to your Web browser from a server and stored on your computer’s hard drive.
Mailing List
YMCA Camp Mohawk, Inc. provides an online form for families wishing to be provided more information about the Mohawk opportunities. This information is securely stored internally and accessed only when we correspond with our mailing list periodically during the year, either via e-mail or regular mail.
Disclosure of Information
YMCA Camp Mohawk Inc. will not disclose any nonpublic personal information to third parties except to the extent necessary and permitted by law.
Changes to This Policy
In the event that YMCA Camp Mohawk, Inc. decides to alter this privacy policy, the changes will be added directly to this statement. We will, however, always use information in accordance with the version of the privacy policy under which it was originally collected.
Contact Us
If you have specific questions or concerns about YMCA Camp Mohawk’s privacy policy, please contact us at info@campmohawk.org.
Keep In Touch to let us know what you’re up to
Your Name (required):
Maiden Name: (if applicable)
Your Email (required)
Years At Mohawk (Ex: 1970-1975)
Address (required)
City (required)
State
AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWashington DCWest VirginiaWisconsinWyoming
Zip Code
Phone
Job Title
Employer
What is your favorite camp memory?
What have you been up to since your time at Mohawk?
x
